<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pan Narrans</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pan Narrans</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Rmarkdown YAML headers</title>
      <link>/post/advanced-rmarkdown-yaml-headers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/advanced-rmarkdown-yaml-headers/</guid>
      <description>Rnotebooks - What and Why? For anyone unfamiliar with Rnotebooks here is a quick overview of why you might want to use them more experienced users can skip ahead. Rnotebooks are scientific notebooks for R, somewhat like jupyter for anyone coming from python but baked right into the Rstudio IDE which offers some benefits over the browser based interface of jupyter. It permits you to organise your code, notes, reasoning and references in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intuitive Explanation of Inferential Distance</title>
      <link>/post/an-intuitive-explanation-of-inferential-distance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/an-intuitive-explanation-of-inferential-distance/</guid>
      <description>Let us represent our beliefs as nodes in a network. Most nodes in your network of beliefs have dependencies, they are connected to other beliefs the truth value of which they are contingent on.
Picture a subset of your network of beliefs, let us take a simplified section that looks like a tree, stripping away the complex interconnections to aid in visualization.
Beliefs B and C are predicated on belief A, beliefs D and E on belief B, and beliefs F and G on belief C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Bias Cards!</title>
      <link>/post/cognitive-bias-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cognitive-bias-cards/</guid>
      <description>Check out the Cognitive Bias Cards Repo for a deck of cards featuring 104 cognitive biases.
Among other things these can be used to play Biased Pandemic: http://lesswrong.com/lw/ar2/biased_pandemic/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>